Guide to the Records of the Bureau of Public Occasions RG.4.2
New York University Archives
- Series I: General Files, 1935-1976; 1950-1975; 33 boxes
  - Real Estate Institute, Annual Dinner and Dance, 1973 February 8 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Real Estate Institute, Annual Dinner and Dance, 1974 March 13 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Real Estate Institute, Annual Dinner and Dance, 1975 April 2 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Regents, New York State Board of, Dinner for, 1958 December 18 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rehabilitation services at NYU, affiliation with Institute for the Crippled and Disabled, 1958 September 25 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Retailing, School of, Conference on Careers, 1962 March 2 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller, Laurence, Nichols Award awarded to, 1963 June 3 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Rome, Irving, Julius Ochs Adler Award awarded to, 1963 May 10 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt, George Emlen, presentation of portrait of, 1965 January 25 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Rosenthal, Ida, Presidential Citation to, 1961 October 25 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Ross, Vincent C., Institute of Accounting Research, Dedication of, 1972 October 5 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Ross Institute, Accounting Seminar, 1973 November 29 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Rubin, Samuel, International Residence Hall, Dedication of, 1964 December 17 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Rubin, Samuel, Presidential Citation to, 1963 November 1 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Russian Educators, Luncheon for, 1958 December 18 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Auditorium (Nichols Hall), Dedication of, 1962 April 4 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1963 February 19 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1963 November 7 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1968 November 14 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1971 April 26 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1971 November 15 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Salomon, Arthur K., Lecture, 1972 December 11 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Salomon Brothers Center for the Study of Financial Institutions, Dedication of, 1974 January 31 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sawhill, President John C., Investiture of: Correspondence (1975 August 27 - November 24), 1975 November 20 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Sawhill, President John C., Investiture of: Invitees, List of, 1975 November 20 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Sawhill, President John C., Investiture of: Photographs, 1975 November 20 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Sawhill, President John C., Investiture of: Printed material, 1975 November 20 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Schedule of Events as of February 17, 1955, 1954 - 1955 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Schimmel, Michael, Auditorium (Tisch Hall), Dedication of, 1972 September 28 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Schwartz, Arthur, Honored by NYU, 1954 May 7 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Lectures, 1967 December 6 - 1968 April 3 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Lectures, 1969 February 26 - April 23 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Lectures, 1972 April 26, May 9 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Senior Class Day Exercises, 1972 May 31 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Senior Class Day Exercises, 1973 June 3 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Shimkin, Leon, Hall, Dedication of, 1973 April 18 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Silver, Julius, Residence Center, Dedication of, 1963 September 25 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Silver Towers, Dedication Reception, 1974 June 3 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, Colloquy, 1963 April 29 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Social Work Recruiting Center of Greater New York, Recruiting Committee Program, 1963 June 20 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Solomon, Louis, Luncheon, 1958 January 15 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Special Events Photographs, 1935-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Special Events Photographs -- Puerto Rico, 1969-1971 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Stevenson, John, Student Study and Lounge, Dedication Ceremony and Reception, 1972 October 6 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Stokes, James, Lecture on Politics, 1957 January 18 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Stokes, James, Lecture on Politics, 1971 February 11 - April 30 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Students, Dinner, 1954 September 23 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1963 February 27 - April 23 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1963 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1964 January 22 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1964 February 26 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1964 April 22 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Students, President's Coffee Hour for, 1964 May 6 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Students, President's Convocation for, 1958 January 28 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Student, Reception for, 1955 June 8 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Student Leaders, Reception for, 1955 December 21 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Student Leaders, Reception for, 1958 October 17 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Suhrawardy, Hussain Shaheed, Prime Minister of Pakistan, University Medal awarded to, 1957 July 26 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Surdna Conference Center (Tisch Hall), Dedication of, 1972 November 3 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Swiss-American Luncheon, 1962 April 10 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Thoreau, Henry David, Hall of Fame Installation, 1962 May 6 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Tisch Hall, Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1969 April 25 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Tisch Hall, Dedication of, 1972 May 17 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Tisch Hall Founders Monument, Dedication of, 1973 May 21 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Tisch Hall Seminar Rooms, Classrooms, Faculty Offices, Dedication of, 1972 November 9 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Tolbert Convocation (President of Liberia), 1976 September 30 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Transfer Students, Presidential Reception for, 1963 September 16 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Transfer Students, Presidential Reception for, 1964 January 31 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - University Architects, Association of, Ninth Annual Conference, 1964 June 2-4 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - University College of Arts and Science, Joint Faculty Meeting, 1964 March 13 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - University Heights Alumni Association, Annual Awards Dinner, 1962 November 20 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - University Heights, Alumni Association, Annual Awards Dinner, 1963 November 19 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - University Heights, Alumni Association, "Alumni and Alumni Relations", 1963 April 15 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - University Heights, Alumni Association, Dinner, Class of '22, 1962 May 25 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - University Heights, Alumni-Faculty, Joint Meeting of, 1963 February 28 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - University Heights, Presbyterian Church, Sermon by James H. Hester, 1964 March 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - University Hospital, Cornerstone Ceremonies, 1961 September 28 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - University Hospital, Diamond Jubilee Convocation, 1957 March 5 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - University Hospital, Founders Day, 1959 September 28 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - University Hospital, Board of, 1963 November 4 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - University Scholars Group, 1963 September 14 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - University Scholars Reception, 1963 October 8 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - University Services Convocation, 1959 September 22 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - University Village, Groundbreaking Ceremonies, 1964 August 12 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - U-Nu Lecture, 1955 July 6 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt Hall, Dedication of, 1951 September 15 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Varsity Club, Annual Sports Award Dinner, 1962 May 28 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Varsity Club, Annual Awards Dinner, 1963 December 2 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Virgin Islands Project, 1963 September 26 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Voorhis, Harold 0., Dinner in honor of, 1961 December 12 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Wald, William D., Hall of Fame Installation, 1971 September 12 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square College, Alumni Association, Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner, 1963 April 27 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square College, Alumni Fund, 1963 December 3 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square College, Alumni Saturday, 1962 April 28 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square College, Coat of Arms Ceremony, 1963 December 17 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Washington Square College, Joint Faculty Meeting, 1964 April 2-4 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Watson, Thomas J., Jr., C. Walter Nichols Award awarded to, 1962 May 9 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Weaver, Warren, Hall, Groundbreaking of, 1962 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Weinstein, Joe, Luncheon in honor of, 1963 May 7 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Weinstein, Joe, Residence Halls, Dedication of, 1963 November 17 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Westchester-Putnam-Rockland Personnel and Guidance Association, Meeting at University Heights Campus, 1963 February 20 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - White, Major Robert M., University Medal awarded to, 1961 September 26 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Whitman, Walt, Centennial, 1955 May 5 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Whitman, Walt, Lecture Series, 1969 April 18, 21, 23, 25 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, Hall of Fame Installation, 1956 May 20 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Women, Conference on Education for, 1959 April 29 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Wriston, Henry M., Security Lecture, 1955 May 6 (Box 33, Folder 27)